Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series IX: 2017 Accretion
  - Susana Lei A'Taua AIR Book, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14-17)
  - Pacific Curricula, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Pacific Session, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Fall 2006 (Box 26, Folder 20-24)
  - Fall 2006 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Palates of Pleasure, 2001-03-19, 2001-03-21 (Box 27, Folder 4-12)
  - Fall 2007 (Box 27, Folder 13-20)
  - Pacific Islands Symposium, 2001-10-25, 2001-10-27 (Box 27, Folder 21-30)
  - Pacific Islands Symposium, 2001-10-25, 2001-10-27 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Model Minority Sessions I & II, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Regie Cabico AIR Book, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
  - Fall 2015 (Box 28, Folder 6-12)
  - Spring 2006, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 13-17)
  - Politics & Paranoia, 2007-04-30, 2007-04-31 (Box 28, Folder 18-21)
  - Co-Sponsorships, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
  - Fall 2012 Public Events (Box 28, Folder 24-28)
  - Fall 2012 Public Events (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
  - Spring 2012 Public Events (Box 29, Folder 5-11)
  - Fall 2013 Events Info (Box 29, Folder 12-18)
  - Fall 2014 (Box 29, Folder 19-24)
  - Spring 2014 Events (Box 29, Folder 25-27)
  - Spring 2014 Events (Box 30, Folder 1-6)
  - Fall 2011 Events (Box 30, Folder 7-9)
  - Spring 2013 Public Events (Box 30, Folder 10-17)
  - Spring 2015 (Box 30, Folder 18-25)